Guide to the Chamberlain-Cravens-Cullinan family papers, 1900-2010 MS 594
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Correspondence, 173567
  - Subseries E: School Records, 173577
    - Subseries F: Births, Marriages, and Deaths, 173578
      - Sympathy Letters regarding Rorick Cravens' death, businesses and organizations, 1976; 173880 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Donations made to Palmer Memorial Church in memory of Rorick Cravens, 1976-1977; 173881 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous Donations made in memory of Rorick Cravens, 1976; 173882 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Sympathy Cards regarding the death of Nina Cullinan, 1983; 173883 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Donations made in memory of Nina Cullinan, 1983; 173884 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Sympathy Letters regarding Margaret Cullinan Wray, 1985; 173885 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Donations made in memory of Margaret Cullinan Wray, 1985; 173886 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Sympathy Cards regarding the death of Mary C. Cullinan Cravens, 1994; 173887 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Funeral Registries and Thank You Note Lists, Mary C. Cullinan Cravens, 1994; 173888 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Sympathy Cards regarding the death of Mary C. Cullinan Cravens, 1994; 173889 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Cards for wedding of J.R. and Mary Cravens, 1929; 173890 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Letters regarding Nancy's birth, 1932; 173891 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Letters regarding Chico's birth, 1933; 173892 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Letters regarding Patsy's birth, 1936; 173893 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Small notes sent with Gifts and Flowers for Children's births, 173894 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous, 173579
    - A.E.'s visit to the states, 173895 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Art Appraisals and Gallery Correspondence, 173896 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Attempts to postpone Charles Chamberlain's Military Service, 173897 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Cards, 173898 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Congratulatory telegrams to Nina Cullinan, undated; 173899 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Farm House, 173900 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Invitations, 173901 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Finances of Estes Park House, 173902 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Specifications of the Estes Park House, 173903 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Telegrams regarding Mary Cravens' Hospital Stay and Operation, 1937; 173904 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Estate of Mary C. Cravens, 1994; 173905 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Estate of Nina Cullinan, 1983; 173906 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Trust Accounts, 173907 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Records from Lucie Cullinan's death, 1929; 173908 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Estate of J. Rorick Cravens (1 of 2), 173909 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Estate of Rorick J. Cravens (2 of 2), 173910 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Legal Documents and Official Statements, 173911 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cravens Parkway, 173912 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Abstract of title to Morse subdivision, 173913 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence fragments, 173914 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified correspondence (with nicknames or illegible), 173915 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Unsigned correspondence, 173916 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Unmatched envelopes, 173917 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Series II: J.S. Cullinan and The Texas Company, 173568
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 173580
    - Allen, Winnie, 173918 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Autry Family, 173919 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: C, 173920 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Cullinan, Craig Jr., 173921 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cullinan, Joe, 173922 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cullinan, John, 173923 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cullinan, J.S., 173924 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Cullinan, Nina, 173925 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Durbin, James H., 173926 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: D-E, 173927 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Flanagan, Frank C., 173928 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: G-H, 173929 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - King, John O., 173930 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Kingsbury, K.R., 173931 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: M-S, 173932 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Sinclair, W.T., 173933 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Tinsley, James, 173934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: W, 173935 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Subseries B: Newspapers, 173581
    - J.S. Cullinan Newspaper Clips, 1917-1982; 173936 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cullinan, Dr. M.P., 1927; 173937 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Healy, James, 173938 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Houston Chamber of Commerce Magazine, 1947, 1952; 173939 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Houston Negro Hospital, 173940 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Houston News, General, 1904-1963; 173941 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Houston Zoo Tiger Attack, 1926; 173942 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Irish Statesman, 1930; 173943 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Mercy Hospital, 1974; 173944 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Philanthropy, 1976-1982; 173945 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Stewart and Stevenson, 1961; 173946 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Strauss, Lewis L., 1974; 173947 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Texas Chamber of Commerce, 173948 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Texas Parade Magazine, 1953; 173949 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Texas Oil Industry, 1920-1938; 173950 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Dinner, 173951 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Tinsley and King Research, 173952 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Series C: Corporate Publications, 173582
    - American Republic Corporation, 173953 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Barber Oil Corporation, 173954 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Harris County Heritage Society Wildcatters Ball, 1978; 173955 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Intracoastal Canal Association, 173956 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Magnolia Petroleum Company, 173957 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Maya Corporation, 173958 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Petroleum Iron Works Company, 173959 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Second National Bank of Houston, 173960 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Standard Oil Company, 173961 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Texaco Publications (1 of 2), 173962 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Texaco Publications (2 of 2), 173963 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Texaco News, 173964 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Texaco Sour Lake Anniversary (1 of 2), 1993; 173965 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Texaco Sour Lake Anniversary (2 of 2), 173966 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Texas Gulf Coast Historical Association, 173967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Subseries D: James Rorick Cravens and Cravens, Dargan & Company, 173583
    - Correspondence: Abshier, Hobby, 173968 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence: Baker, Botts, Parker & Garwood, 173969 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence: Blodgett, W.A., 173970 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence: Cravens, Augusta, 173971 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence: Cravens, James, 173972 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence: Cravens, Rorick, 173973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence: C-D, 173974 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence: G-H, 173975 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence: Kirkland, William, 173976 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence: L-N, 173977 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence: O-R, 173978 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence: Reorden, Dwight P., 173979 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence: S-W, 173980 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Cravens, Dargan & Company Publications, 173981 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - The Cravens Primer, 1929-1969; 173982 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Newsclippings: Cravens, James, 173983 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Newsclippings: Cravens, James Rorick, 173984 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Newspaper: Cravens, Dargan & Company, 173985 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Newspaper: Gulf Coast Investment Corporation, 173986 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Newspaper: Second National Bank of Houston, 173987 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Newspaper: Texas Commerce Bank, 173988 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Newspaper: The Wyatt Way, 1953; 173989 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Texas Fund Incorporated, 173990 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Cravens Ranch Appraisal, 1992-1993; 173991 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Series III: Photographs, 173569
  - Subseries A: Chamberlain Family Photos, 173584
    - Chamberlain, 174083 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Chamberlain Family, 1990-99; 174084 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Chamberlain Family, 2000; 174085 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Chamberlain Family, undated; 174086 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Chamberlain Family Portraits, 174087 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Chamberlain, Anne, 174088 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Chamberlain, Charles III, 174089 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Chamberlain, Daniel, 174090 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Chamberlain, Mary, 174091 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Chamberlain, Nancy (1 of 2), 174092 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Chamberlain, Nancy (2 of 2), 174093 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - N. Chamberlain Slides, 1986; 174094 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 174095 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 1997; 174096 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 2000; 174097 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, Trip to Europe, 2000; 174098 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 2001; 174099 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 2002; 174100 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, 2003; 174101 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, Trip to Europe, 2005; 174102 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - N. Chamberlain Family, Cards, 174103 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Weddings, 174104 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Subseries B: Cravens Family Photos, 173585
    - Cravens (1 of 3), 174106 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Cravens (2 of 3), 174107 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cravens (3 of 3), 174108 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Augusta Tuttle Cravens (Donna), 174109 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - James Cravens, 174110 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - James Cravens: House at 3416 Montrose Boulevard, 174111 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - James "Chico" Cravens, 174112 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Malcom Cravens, 174113 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Mary Cravens, 174114 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Nancy Tuttle Ferguson Cravens, 174115 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Rorick Cravens, 174116 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - J.A. Howse, 174117 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Blasmer Brigade at Farm & Galveston, 174118 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Boston, 1926-1927; 174119 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Bronxville, NY, 174120 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Cheyenne (1 of 2), 1923; 174121 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cheyenne (2 of 2), 1923; 174122 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Corsicana Farm, 1913; 174123 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Deer Park, 1917; 174124 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Eden, 174125 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Friends and Family, 1912-1913; 174126 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Fort Worth Trip, 1928; 174127 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - High School, 174128 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Josephine Stich, 174129 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Lake Placid Club, 174130 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Landscape, 174131 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Linville, 174132 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Katy Ruth, Nina, Mary C., 174133 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Killarrey, 174134 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Lucy Cullinan and Family, 174135 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Maplewood Golf Links, undated; 174136 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Mount Park, 174137 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Niagara Falls, 1913; 174138 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Shadyside, 1919; 174139 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Sugar Hill Farm, 1913; 174140 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Summer Farm, 1918; 174141 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified, 1917; 174142 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified, 1925; 174143 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified, 1927; 174144 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified, undated; 174145 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Vacations: Alaska, 174146 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Vacations: Alaska, Canada, Glacier Park, 174147 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Vacations: Colorado, 1918; 174148 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Vacations: Greece, Scotland, Turkey, 174149 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Vacations: Mexico, 174150 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Vacations: Montana, Canada, 1927; 174151 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Vacations: U.K. (1 of 2), 174152 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Vacations: U.K. (2 of 2), 174153 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Vacations: Unidentified, 1929; 174154 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Vacations: Yellowstone, 174155 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Subseries C: Cullinan Family Photos, 174034
    - Cullinan, J.S. Family, 174035 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Cullinan, Children of J.S., 174036 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Cullinan, Grandchildren of J.S., 174037 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Cullinan, undated; 174038 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Cullinan Photo Album, 174039 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Anna Cullinan, 174040 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Craig Cullinan, Jr., 174041 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - John Cullinan, 174042 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - J.S. Cullinan (1 of 2), 174043 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - J.S. Cullinan (2 of 2), 174044 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - J.S. Cullinan: Friends, 174045 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - J.S. Cullinan: House, Corsicana TX, 174046 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - J.S. Cullinan: House, 1603 Rusk Avenue, 174047 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - J.S. Cullinan: House, Santa Ana Farm, 174048 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - J.S. Cullinan: House, Shadyside, 174049 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - John Cullinan, 174050 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Lucie Halm Cullinan, 174051 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Nina Cullinan, 174052 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Cullinan Park Dedication, 1982; 174053 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Houston Negro hospital (Riverside General) Dedication, 174054 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Launching of Cape Beale, 1944; 174055 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Lake George, Middleton, 1926; 174056 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Postcards, 174057 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Shadyside, 174058 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Smith College, 174059 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified Vacations, 174060 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified, undated; 174061 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Watt's Ranch, Albany, 1925; 174062 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Family Groups, Cullinan-Cravens-Chamberlain, 174063 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Ferguson, 174064 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Todd, 174065 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Subseries D: General Photos, 174067
    - Buildings, 174068 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Graves, 174069 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Landscapes, 174070 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pets, 174071 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified, 1930s; 174072 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified, 1940s; 174073 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified, 1950s; 174074 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified, 1960s; 174075 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified (1 of 2), undated; 174076 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified (2 of 2), undated; 174077 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Friends, Family, Adults, 174078 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Friends, Family, Children, 174079 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Portraits, 174080 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Vacations, 174081 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Vehicles, 174082 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - SubSeries E: Oversized Photographs, 174066
    - Cullinan Photographs (Box 15)
    - Cullinan-Cravens photographs (Box 16)
  - Subseries F: Negatives, 173586
    - Bear Creek, 174156 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bronxville, New York, 174157 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Canada and Alaska, 1914; 174158 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Cheyenne, 1923; 174159 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Clearlake, 174160 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Cravens, 1951; 174161 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Cravens, 1952; 174162 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Country Club, 174163 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Cravens, 1968; 174164 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Cravens, Unidentified, undated; 174165 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - R. Cravens, 1962; 174166 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Deer Park, 1917; 174167 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Eden, 174168 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Europe Relatives, 1922; 174169 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Fort Worth Trip, 1928; 174170 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Garden of the Gods, 174171 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Glacier National, 1914; 174172 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Glenwood Springs, Colorado, 174173 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Grand Canyon, 174174 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - High School, 174175 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - House Party, 1918; 174176 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - "Home", 174177 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Kent Place, 174178 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Lake George, 1922; 174179 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Lake George, 1926; 174180 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Linville, 1929; 174181 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Park, 174182 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Maplewood, 1913; 174183 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Mary Cullinan, 174184 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Methodist Picnic, 174185 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Mexico, 174186 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia, 174187 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - "Roof + K.S.", 174188 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - School, 174189 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - South Colorado, 1921; 174190 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Shennile Ranch, 174191 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Summer Farm, 1918; 174192 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified, 1915; 174193 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified, 1917; 174194 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified, 1918; 174195 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified, 1925; 174196 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified, 1927; 174197 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1949; 174198 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated; 174199 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Waterford City, 174200 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Waterford City, "War", 174201 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Watts Ranch, Albany, 1925; 174202 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Yosemite, 174203 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - N. Chamberlain, 174204 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Mary C. Cullinan Cravens, 174205 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Cullinan, 174206 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified, undated; 174207 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Subseries G: Slides, 173587 (Box 17a)
- Series IV: Genealogy, 173570
  - Subseries A: Books, 173588
    - Beavers, Joseph, A History of, 1948; 174234 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Bovard, Sarah, Diary, 1859; 174235 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chamberlain Association of America, 1908; 174236 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Cravens, The House of, 1972; 174237 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Dawson, Robert, Descendants of, 1874; 174238 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Douglas Register, 1750-1797; 174239 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - English, Thomas Descendants, 1986; 174240 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Fergusson, Ferguson, Fergus Records, 1895; 174241 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Gordons of Nethermur, 1913; 174242 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Harrison, Benjamin Ancestry, 1893; 174243 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Harrison, Settlers by the Long Grey Trail, 174244 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Henderson Chronicles, 1915; 174245 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Henderson Family Records, 1672-1865; 174246 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Melungeons, Yesterday and Today, 174247 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kryder Family History, Volume I, 1736-1803; 174248 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Kryder Family History, Volume II, 1736-1803; 174249 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Lamb, Rose and Others: Genealogy, 1904; 174250 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - House of Cravens, 174251 (Box 19)
    - Murphy Family, 2001; 174252 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Patterson, James and his Descendants, 1925; 174253 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Patterson & Johnston, Concerning the Forefathers, 1902; 174254 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pollard, Jonathan: Ancestry & Descendants, 1891; 174255 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Roberts Family, Early History of, 174256 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Simmendinger Register, 1709; 174257 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Solana Ranch Stanzas, Rorick Cravens, undated; 174258 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Townsend Brothers, Memorial, 1865; 174259 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Tuttle, James & Rebecca: Descendants of: Solomon Tuttle, 174260 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Tuttle/Tuthill, Lines in America, 1968; 174261 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: E-mails (by family), 173589
    - Aikens, Valencia, 174262 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Allen/Blackman Family, 174263 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Barton Family, 174264 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Beall Family, 174265 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Beavers, 174266 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Black Family, 174267 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Boone Family, 174268 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Carrigh, 174269 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Chamberlain (1 of 3), 174270 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Chamberlain (2 of 3), 179048 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Chamberlain (3 of 3), 179049 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Cherokee Blood Line, 179050 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Clerkin, 179051 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Considine, 179052 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Cravens (1 of 3), 179053 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Cravens (2 of 3), 179054 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Cravens (3 of 3), 179058 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Crume, 179055 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cullinan (1 of 2), 179056 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cullinan (2 of 2), 179057 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Dawson (1 of 2), 179059 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dawson (2 of 2), 179060 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Declan, 179061 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Dennis Family, 179062 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Dubque, 179063 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Ellis, 179064 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - English Family (1 of 4), 179065 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - English Family (2 of 4), 179066 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - English Family (3 of 4), 179067 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - English Family (4 of 4), 179068 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Ferguson (1 of 2), 179069 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Ferguson (2 of 2), 179070 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Gordon, 179071 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Hale, Pau, 179072 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Halm, 179073 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Hampton, Andrew, 179074 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Harrison (1 of 2), 179075 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Harrison (2 of 2), 179076 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Hazelhurst, 179077 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Hill, Robert, 179078 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Holser, 179079 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Johnston Family, 179080 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Keeton Family, 179081 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Lamme, 179082 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Love, 179083 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Magill Family, 179084 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Mareck Family, 179085 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Murphy (1 of 2), 179086 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Murphy (2 of 2), 179087 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Kinnan, 179088 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Kryder Family, 179089 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - McDowell, Elizabeth, 179090 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Mills, 179091 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Nara, 179092 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Nelson, Patricia, 179093 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Nickell Family, 179094 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Patterson (1 of 2), 179095 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Patterson (2 of 2), 179096 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Pegelow, Katie, 179097 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Phillips, Judy, 179098 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Plemmons, 179099 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Pollard, 179100 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Quapaw Indians, 179101 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Rivas, Barbara, 179102 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Rose Family, 179103 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Roberts Family, 179104 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Rogen, 179105 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Scott Family, 179106 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Thomas and Rebecca, 179107 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Stewart, 179108 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Stump Family, 179109 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Todd, David, 179110 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Townsend Family, 179111 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Tuttles Family, 179112 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Wallace, Don, 179113 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Wharfedale Family, 179114 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Wright, 179115 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Young Family, 179116 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Subseries C: E-mails (by geographic region), 173590
    - Arkansas, 179117 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - California, Solano County, 179118 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Delaware, 179119 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - England, Bristol, 179120 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - England, Yorkshire County, 179121 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Germany, 179122 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Iowa, 179123 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Ireland, Clare County (1 of 3), 179124 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Ireland, Clare County (2 of 3), 179125 (Box 23, Folder 1)